Guide to the David Sullivan U.S. Maoism Collection TAM 527
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series V: Union Organizing, 1961-1988
  Series V contains material related to the union organizing work of David Sullivan. It is presumed that these materials relate to work he himself engaged with, but there could also be material related to work he simply collected on. The Series is broken down by union, first the United Autoworkers and then the United Steelworkers of America. This Series highlights the activities of rank and file activists within these two unions and their various locals. Material from the United Autoworkers largely comes from the ALCOA plant in Cleveland and includes a folder of grievances that Sullivan filed with the union. There are numerous locals represented from the United Steelworkers of America, most with small runs of bulletins and newsletters from rank and file activists within the local. These include Local 1014's Coke Plant Breeze and the Mill Hunk Herald. Political fliers and brochures related to the campaign of James Balanoff for President of District 31 are found in this Series as well as material related to other union election campaigns.
  - United Autoworkers, 1976, undated (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - United Autoworkers (ALCOA), 1973-1974, undated (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - United Autoworkers: The ALCOA News, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - United Autoworkers: Cleveland Communicator, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - United Autoworkers: H-Plant (ALCOA), 1974 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - United Autoworkers: Local 588, 1981, undated (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - United Autoworkers: Local 808 (ALCOA), 1974, undated (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - United Autoworkers: Local 980: "Concerned Autoworkers", undated (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - United Autoworkers: Local 1050, 1974-1974, undated (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - United Autoworkers: Local 1050: "Concerned Autoworkers" (ALCOA), undated (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - United Autoworkers: Local 1250, undated (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - United Autoworkers: Local 1631, undated (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - United Autoworkers: People Get Ready, undated (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - United Autoworkers: Sullivan, David: Grievance Reports (ALCOA), 1974-1975, undated (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - United Autoworkers: Unity (workers organization), undated (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - United Steelworkers of America: 1984 Elections (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - United Steelworkers of America: Agreements, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - United Steelworkers of America: Bibliography, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - United Steelworkers of America: Circular Letters, 1980-1988 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - United Steelworkers of America: Credit Unions, 1961, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - United Steelworkers of America: District 27/28 Steelworkers Organizing Committee, undated (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - United Steelworkers of America: District 31, 1979-1981 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - United Steelworkers of America: District 31: Balanoff, James Campaign, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - United Steelworkers of America: District 31: Balanoff, James Campaign: Election Observer Credentials, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - United Steelworkers of America: District 31: Germano, Joseph (Director, biographical sketch), 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - United Steelworkers of America: District 31: Parton, Jack Campaign, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - United Steelworkers of America: District 31: Women's Caucus, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - United Steelworkers of America: Division 10: Lukehart, John Campaign for Griever, undated (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - United Steelworkers of America: Elections (union), 1979, undated (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - United Steelworkers of America: Fliers, 1974-1980 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - United Steelworkers of America: History, undated (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - United Steelworkers of America: International Committee against Racism (INCAR), undated (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - United Steelworkers of America: Keith Anwar Defense Committee, 1979-1981 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - United Steelworkers of America: Local 65, 1980-1983, undated (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - United Steelworkers of America: Local 201: Women's Committee, 1981, undated (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - United Steelworkers of America: Local 1010, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - United Steelworkers of America: Local 1010: Labor History Calendars, 1979-1985 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - United Steelworkers of America: Local 1010: Negotiating Committee, undated (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - United Steelworkers of America: Local 1010: Women's Committee, undated (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - United Steelworkers of America: Local 1011: Fight for Jobs Committee, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - United Steelworkers of America: Local 1014, 1978-1983 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - United Steelworkers of America: Local 1014: Circular Letters, 1983-1985 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - United Steelworkers of America: Local 1014: Coke Plant Breeze, 1979-1983 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - United Steelworkers of America: Local 1014: Journal, 1981-1984 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - United Steelworkers of America: Local 1014: Sullivan, David: Membership Card, Correspondence regarding, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - United Steelworkers of America: Local 1014: Union Politics, undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - United Steelworkers of America: Local 1014: Unity and Unified Slate, 1979-1982 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - United Steelworkers of America: Local 1014: Women's Committee, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - United Steelworkers of America: Local 1026: Rank and File, circa 1980 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - United Steelworkers of America: Local 1033, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - United Steelworkers of America: Local 1033: Committee for a Fighting Union, 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - United Steelworkers of America: Local 1053: Interlake Local 1053 Social Club, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - United Steelworkers of America: Local 1219: Weisen, Ron Support for, undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - United Steelworkers of America: Local 1397, undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - United Steelworkers of America: Local 1462 (pamphlet), undated (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - United Steelworkers of America: Local 1527: The Steelworker, undated (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - United Steelworkers of America: Local 2322: Ripe Mill Report, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - United Steelworkers of America: Local 2609: Concerned Members of 2609, undated (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - United Steelworkers of America: Local 2632, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - United Steelworkers of America: Local 3059, undated (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - United Steelworkers of America: Local 15271, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - United Steelworkers of America: Machine Shop News, undated (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - United Steelworkers of America: Machineshop Chatter, undated (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - United Steelworkers of America: McKee, Frank Campaign for President, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - United Steelworkers of America: Mill Hunk Herald, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - United Steelworkers of America: NIPSCO, 1980, undated (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - United Steelworkers of America: On Track (Hammond Freight Division), 1979 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - United Steelworkers of America: Pamphlets and Publications, 1982, undated (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - United Steelworkers of America: Rank and File, 1979-1981 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - United Steelworkers of America: Save Jobs Committee (Youngstown, OH), undated (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - United Steelworkers of America: Sheet Mill News, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - United Steelworkers of America: Sparrows Point, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - United Steelworkers of America: Steel Unity, undated (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - United Steelworkers of America: Steel Worker Rights (Cleveland, OH), 1977 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - United Steelworkers of America: Steel Workers Fight Back, undated (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - United Steelworkers of America: The Steelworker (Cleveland, OH), 1977, undated (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - United Steelworkers of America: Steelworkers (Bell, CA), undated (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - United Steelworkers of America: Steelworkers Defense Committee: John Mullins Family Fundraiser, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - United Steelworkers of America: Steelworkers for Sadlowski, 1973, undated (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - United Steelworkers of America: Steelworkers for the Right to Ratify and Right to Strike, undated (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - United Steelworkers of America: Steelworkers Know-Your-Ducks Committee, undated (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - United Steelworkers of America: Tri-State Conference on the Impact of Steel, 1981, undated (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - United Steelworkers of America: United States Steel Corporation, 1981-1986, undated (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - United Steelworkers of America: USX Lockout, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - United Steelworkers of America: Weber Case (affirmative action), undated (Box 8, Folder 43)
- Series VI: Subject Files, 1938-1987
  Series VI consists of files of material identified by subject. These files contain clippings, minutes and notes from meetings, pamphlets, and other publications related to the topic at hand. The handwritten minutes and notes within these files suggest that the creator of them was involved with the organizations represented, such as the National Lawyers Guild and the Vietnam Veterans Against the War. The other major subject represented in the files is related to women's rights generally, abortion and the equal rights amendment more specifically. Of particular note, this Series contains material related to a fundraising effort of David Sullivan, whereby he was selling the poetry of influential communist Leibel Bergman in order to raise money for Bergman's bills. Volumes of Bergman's poetry can be found here, as well as a part of his FBI file.
  - Abortion, 1979-1980, undated (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Anti-Imperialist Community Organization, undated (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Bergman, Leibel: FBI File (partial), undated (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Bergman, Leibel: Poetry Fundraiser, 1946, 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - China Visit, 1977, undated (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Circular Letters (from various unidentified sources), 1970-1979, undated (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Citizens Party, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Equal Rights Amendment, 1976-1980 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Food Crisis, undated (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Hospital Workers (New York, NY), 1977 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - International Women's Day, 1971-1982, undated (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Medical Committee For Human Rights, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - National Lawyers Guild, 1977-1979 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - National Lawyers Guild: Chicago Chapter, 1974-1980 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - National Lawyers Guild: Chicago Chapter: Law Student Organizing Committee, undated (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - National Lawyers Guild: Chicago Chapter: Newsletter, 1977-1979 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - National Lawyers Guild: Chicago-Kent Chapter, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - National Lawyers Guild: Conventions, 1977-1983 (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - National Lawyers Guild: Gay Caucus, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - National Lawyers Guild: Labor Work, 1978-1980 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - National Lawyers Guild: Meeting Minutes and Notes, 1977-1979 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - National Lawyers Guild: Milwaukee Regional, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - National Lawyers Guild: National Committee To Combat Women's Oppression I, 1979-1982 (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - National Lawyers Guild: National Committee To Combat Women's Oppression II, 1979-1982 (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - National Lawyers Guild: National Executive Board, 1975-1981 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - National Lawyers Guild: National Lawyers Guild Law Student Clearinghouse, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - National Lawyers Guild: New York City Chapter, 1978-1980 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - National Lawyers Guild: Pamphlets and Publications, 1980, undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - National Lawyers Guild: Twin Cities Chapter, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Notes/ Notebooks (unidentified organizations), 1972, undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Notes/ Notebooks (unidentified organizations) I, circa 1981, undated (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Notes/ Notebooks (unidentified organizations) II, circa 1981, undated (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Notes/ Notebooks (unidentified organizations), undated (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Outlaw (postal workers), undated (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Party Building, 1978-1981 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Philippines, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Political Economy, undated (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Political Education, undated (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Political Education, undated (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Political Education: Outlines I, undated (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - Political Education: Outlines II, undated (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - Political Education: Outlines III, undated (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - Political Education (Workers School), 1938 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Prisoners, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Reproductive Health Hazards, 1979-1981 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Reproductive Rights National Network, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Revolutionary Student Brigade, 1975-1980 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Right Wing, 1979-1981 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Socialist Feminism, undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Statistical Reports: New York and New Jersey I, undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Statistical Reports: New York and New Jersey II, undated (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Students For A Democratic Society, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Study Tour To The People's Republic Of China, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Unemployed Workers Organizing Committee, undated (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Vietnam Veterans Against the War, undated (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Vietnam Veterans Against the War: Anti-Imperialist Minority Faction, undated (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Vietnam Veterans Against the War: Buffalo Chapter: Prison And Political Defense Committee, undated (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Vietnam Veterans Against the War: Chicago Chapter, 1981, undated (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Vietnam Veterans Against the War: Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Vietnam Veterans Against the War: Fliers, undated (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Vietnam Veterans Against the War: "The Guidon National Newsletter", undated (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Vietnam Veterans Against the War: "Inside-Out: Same Struggle-Same Fight" (newsletter For prisoners), 1975 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Vietnam Veterans Against the War: Milwaukee Chapter, undated (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Vietnam Veterans Against the War: Minority Report, undated (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Vietnam Veterans Against the War: National Campaign, undated (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Vietnam Veterans Against the War: National Office, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Vietnam Veterans Against the War: National Steering Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Vietnam Veterans Against the War: New Jersey Chapter, undated (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Vietnam Veterans Against the War: New York Chapter, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Vietnam Veterans Against the War: New York-Northern New Jersey Region, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Vietnam Veterans Against the War: Newsletters, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Vietnam Veterans Against the War: Pamphlets And Publications, undated (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Vietnam Veterans Against the War: Petitions, undated (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Vietnam Veterans Against the War: Position Papers, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Vietnam Veterans Against the War: Program Proposals, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Vietnam Veterans Against the War: Regional Reports, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Vietnam Veterans Against the War: "The Returning Black Vietnam-Era Veteran", undated (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Vietnam Veterans Against the War: Songs, undated (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Vietnam Veterans Against the War: Trenton Chapter, undated (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Vietnam Veterans Against the War: Workshop Reports, undated (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Violence Against Women And Pornography, 1978-1981 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Weatherman, undated (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Women and Poverty, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Women Employed, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Women in Law, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Women Organized for Reproductive Choice, 1979-1981 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Women's Bibliography, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Women's Healthcare, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Worker's Liberation Army Manual, undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Series VII: Organizational Printed Ephemera, 1938-2006
  Series VII makes up the largest portion of the collection and contains folders of material documenting the printed and public matter produced by hundreds of U.S. leftist organizations. Contained within the files are brochures, fliers, pamphlets, and other publications. A majority of the organizations were affiliated with the U.S. Marxist-Leninist-Maoist tradition, such as the August 29th Movement, the Bay Area Communist Union, the Black Workers Congress, Freedom Road Socialist Organization, and the October League.
  - 1026 Rank And File (United Steelworkers of America), undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - A. Philip Randolph Institute, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Abortion Rights Action Week, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Academic Freedom Committee (Bennington College, Vermont), circa 1994 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Ad Hoc Committee For A Conference On The International Situation (New York, NY), 1976 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Affirmative Action Coalition of Chicago, undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Africa Research Group (South Africa), 1971 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - African Liberation Day Coalition (Washington DC), 1977 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - African Liberation Support Committee, circa 1977 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - African People's Party, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Afro-Asian Latin American Peoples' Solidarity Forum (Seattle, WA), 1976 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Albania, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Albania, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Alliance To End Repression (Cairo, IL), 1970s (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Amalgamated Clothing And Textile Workers Union: Rank And File, undated (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - American Civil Liberties Union (anti-draft registration), 1980 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - American Civil Liberties Union (reproductive rights), 1981 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - American Friends Service Committee, 1968-1977 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - American Friends Service Committee: Program On Government Surveillance And Citizens Rights (Jackson, MS), 1978 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - American Working Class: Statistical Reports, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Anarchos (ecology), undated (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Angola Solidarity Committee (London), 1975 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Angola Support Conference (Chicago, IL), 1976 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Anti-Bakke Decision Coalition, 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Appalachian Movement Press, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Ashby Leach Defense Committee, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Asian-Americans/ Asian National Question (United Front Against Imperialism), 1974 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Attica (general), undated (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Attica Brigade, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Attica Defense Fund, undated (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - August 29th Movement (ATM), 1974-1976 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Autoworkers United To Fight I, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Autoworkers United To Fight II, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Bailly Alliance (Gary, Indiana), 1980 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Balanoff, Miriam Campaign for State Representative, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Baraka, Imamu Amiri, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Barrio Unido, undated (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Bay Area Communist Union, 1976-1978 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Bay Area Radical Education Project (women's liberation), undated (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Bell Worker's Action Committee/ Strike Back, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Berkeley Liberation Program, undated (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Big Bill Haywood Books (Yellow Springs, OH), 1972 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Black Anti-Imperialist Student Caucus, undated (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Black Liberation, undated (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Black Liberation Month, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - Black Lung Bill (HR 10760), undated (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Black Panther Party, 1968-1970 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Black Panther Party: New York Chapter, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Black Workers Congress, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Black Workers Congress, undated (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Black Workers Organizing Committee, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Bronx Coalition (Nelson Rockefeller, Attica uprising), undated (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - The Brown Underground (UPS), undated (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Build the Resistance: Draft, undated (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Bulletin (unknown organization), 1978 (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Busing, 1975-1980 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Cambion 3 Defense Committee, undated (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - Cambodia Relief Now, undated (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - CDE Strike (Boston, MA), undated (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - Center for Constitutional Rights, 2006, undated (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - Center for United Labor Action (New York, NY), 1971, undated (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - Central Intelligence Agency (job application), undated (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - Central Organization of U.S. Marxist-Leninists (Chicago, IL), 1974, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Chicago May Day Coalition, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - Chile Solidarity Committee (New York, NY), 1974 (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - China Books and Periodicals, undated (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - China Visit (photograph), undated (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - C.H.R.Y. R.U.M. (Highland Park, MI) (black liberation), undated (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - Citizens Against Nuclear Power (Chicago, IL), 1980 (Box 10, Folder 69)
  - Citizens Party, 1980-1982 (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - Class Analysis (Emoryville, CA), 1975 (Box 10, Folder 70)
  - Cleveland Committee to Support the Palestinian People, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 71)
  - Cleveland Rubber Strike Support Committee, 1976, undated (Box 10, Folder 72)
  - Cleveland Sign the Treaty Now Coalition, undated (Box 10, Folder 73)
  - Cleveland Worker, undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Closer To It (Akron, Ohio), 1974 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Coalition Against Registration and the Draft (Chicago, IL), undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Coalition for a New Foreign and Military Policy (Washington DC), 1981 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Coalition in Support of Democratic Kampuchea, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Coalition of Labor Union Women: Chicago Chapter, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Collinswood United Front, undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Colorado Organization For Revolutionary Struggle, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Comic Book/ Graphic Book (in Chinese), 1971 (Box 11, Folder 8a)
  - Comite de Trabajadores, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Committee Against the Kidnapping of Tina Fishman's Daughter, undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Committee for a Decent and Equal Education, undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Committee for a Just Settlement in Iran, undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Committee for an Independent Cyprus, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Committee in Support of the Iranian People, undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Committee to Defend Carlos Feliciano (New York, NY), undated (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Committee to Defend the Community, undated (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Committee to Elect/ Re-Elect Mayor Washington (Chicago, IL), 1980s (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Committee to Fight Energy Rip-Offs, undated (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Committee to Free Bornson and Davis, undated (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Committee to Save CCH (Cook County Hospital), 1980 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Committee to Smash the No-Strike Deal, undated (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Common Dreams (bumper stickers), undated (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Communist League, 1970-1972 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Communist Organizational Chart, undated (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Communist Party of Australia (Marxist-Leninist), 1979 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Communist Party of Britain Marxist-Leninist, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Communist Party of Colombia (Marxist-Leninist), 1978 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Communist Party of Germany, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Communist Party of Ireland, undated (Box 11, Folder 29)